

const data4 = {

    topic: "JavaScript",
    timelimit: 20,

    paper:
        [
            {
                "Question": "this is first Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4", "opt5", "opt6"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "this is second Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "this is Third Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            }
        ]
}

const data2 = {

    topic: "JavaScript",
    timelimit: 20,

    paper:
        [
            {
                "Question": "this is first Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4", "opt5", "opt6"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "this is second Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "this is Third Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            }
        ]
}

const data3 = {

    topic: "JavaScript",
    timelimit: 20,

    paper:
        [
            {
                "Question": "this is first Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4", "opt5", "opt6"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "this is second Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "this is Third Question",
                "options": ["opt1", "opt2", "opt3", "opt4"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            }
        ]
}

const data1 = {

    topic: "HTML and CSS",
    timelimit: 20,

    paper:
        [
            {
                "Question": `In below code snippet, in what order will the margins be added?
                p {
                    margin: 25px 50px 75px 100px:
                }
                `,
                "options": ["Top, Right, Bottom, Left", "Top, Left, Bottom, Right", "Top, Bottom, Right, Left", "Right, Left, Top, Bottom "],
                "correct": "Top, Right, Bottom, Left"
            },
            {
                "Question": "You are working on a form. You want to allow users to make multiple selections. Select the best control.",
                "options": ["Radio button", "textArea", "Checkbox", "Radio or checkbox"],
                "correct": "Checkbox"
            },
            {
                "Question": "How can you ensure that all necessary fields are populated before a form can be submitted?",
                "options": ["Write a JavaScript function to evaluate all the controls on the form of content.",
                    "On the server , evaluates all the controls for data and returns an error page for missing content.",
                    "Add the required attribute on each control so the user gets a message that the field is required.",
                    "Add a label to the page to let users know which controls they must fill in."],
                "correct": "Add the required attribute on each control so the user gets a message that the field is required."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which of the following CSS properties can be used for hiding an element in the DOM without changing the layout of the page?",
                "options": ["display='none'", "visibility='none'", "visibility='hidden'", "display='hidden'"],
                "correct": "visibility='hidden'"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which of the following statements will apply a box shadow to the right and bottom edge of a div element?",
                "options": ["box-shadow: black 5px 5px;", "box-shadow: black -5px 5px;", "box-shadow: black 5px -5px;", "box-shadow: black -5px -5px;"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which of the following CSS property for position would place an element relative to the browser window?",
                "options": ["Absolute", "Fixed", "Relative", "sticky"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Absolute positioning positions an object relative to what?",
                "options": ["The top-left corner of the browser window",
                    "The top-left corner of its parent element",
                    "Centered inside the window",
                    "Centered inside its parent element"],
                "correct": "The top-left corner of its parent element"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which transformation enables you to change the size of an element?",
                "options": ["rotate", "skew", "translate", "scale"],
                "correct": "scale"
            },
            {
                "Question": "You are working with the web storage api. You want to ensure that the data you stored is cleared when the user closes the browser. Where should you store it?",
                "options": ["LocalStorage", "cookieStorage", "sessionStorage", "A hidden input element"],
                "correct": "sessionStorage"
            },
            {
                "Question": "You are working on a web page . you are looking from the outside edge of an element and moving to the inside edge. Select the right order that the padding, margin, and border occur in?",
                "options": ["padding, border, margin",
                    "margin, border, padding",
                    "border, padding, margin",
                    "margin, padding, border"],
                "correct": "margin, border, padding"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which of the following is the way to configure the amount of space between words?",
                "options": ["word-margin", "letter-margin", "word-spacing", "word-padding"],
                "correct": "word-spacing"
            },
            {
                "Question": "How can you create a semi-transparent background color?",
                "options": ["background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.5);",
                 "background-color: rgbx(0,0,0,0.5);",
                  "background-color: hsl(0,0,0,0.5);",
                   "background-color: rgba(0,0,0,1);"],
                "correct": "background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.5);"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which property is used to adjust the space between text characters?",
                "options": ["Text-transform", "font-variant", "font-style", "letter-spacing"],
                "correct": "letter-spacing"
            },
            {
                "Question": "What are the uses of CSS pseudo-elements?",
                "options": ["Style specified parts of an element.",
                 "Style the first letter or line of an element.", 
                 "insert content before or after the element.",
                  "All of the above."],
                "correct": "All of the above."
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which of the following CSS properties specifies the stack order of elements?",
                "options": ["z-index", "overlap", "No such specific property is present", "None of the above"],
                "correct": "opt1"
            },
            {
                "Question": "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is?",
                "options": ["opacity", "visibility", "filter", "None of the above"],
                "correct": "opacity"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Can negative values be allowed in padding property?",
                "options": ["Yes", "No", "Depends on property", "None of the above"],
                "correct": "No"
            },
            {
                "Question": "Which of the following colors contain equal amount of RGB?",
                "options": ["White", "Gray", "Black", "All of the above"],
                "correct": "All of the above"
            },
            {
                "Question": "What is the speciality about the <small> and <big> tags in HTML",
                "options": ["They work on anything", "They can be used for text only", "They can be repeated", "None of the above"],
                "correct": "They can be repeated"
            },
            {
                "Question": "What is the correct order to effectively apply CSS.",
                "options": ["a:link, a:visited, a:hover, a:acitive", "a:acitive, a:hover, a:link, a:visited", "a:hover, a:visited, a:link, a:acitive", "a:visited, a:link, a:active, a:hover"],
                "correct": "a:link, a:visited, a:hover, a:acitive"
            }

        ]
}

export { data1, data2, data3, data4 };
